《暮光之城4：破晓（上）》
Childhood is not from birth to a certain age.
童年并非从出生到某一年龄的时间段
At a certain age the child is grown and puts away childish things.
到了一定岁数 孩子会长大 抛开幼稚的东西
Childhood is the kingdom where nobody dies.
童年是没有生老病死的国度
Jake! Jacob!
杰克 雅各布
(新娘:伊莎贝拉·玛丽·斯旺 | 新郎:爱德华·安东尼·马森·卡伦)
Phil!
菲尔
It's happening.
终于盼来了
You just have to break them in.
你只要练习一下就好了
I've been breaking them in for 3 days.
我都练了3天了
- Can I just go barefoot? - No!
- 我能光着脚吗？- 不
Absolutely not!
绝对不行
I'm thinking it's just a little much,you know?
我觉得这有点过了 不是吗？
The dress and the shoes...
婚纱 鞋子
All of this.
所有这些
No,it's exactly enough.
不 这很重要
Tomorrow will be perfect.
明天会非常完美
Where you want'em,boss?
放哪儿 老板娘？
On either side of the aisle.
通道的两边
- What aisle? - Does no one have vision?
- 什么通道？- 没人长眼睛吗？
You! Go home and gets lots of beauty sleep.
你 快回家睡个美容觉
That's an order.
这是命令
OK...
好吧
I'm just checking for cold feet.
我只是看看你有没有紧张得手脚冰凉
Mine are toasty warm.
我的脚热乎乎的
It's not too late to change your mind.
现在改变主意还不晚
You're having second thoughts?
你有其它想法了？
You are?
有吗？
I've waited a century to marry you,Ms. Swan.
我为娶你已经等了一个世纪 斯旺小姐
But?
可是？
I haven't told you everything about myself.
你并不了解我的全部
What? You're not a virgin?
不了解什么？你不是处男？
You can't scare me away now.
你现在别想把我吓跑
A few years after Carlisle created me,
卡莱尔把我变成吸血鬼的几年后
I rebelled against him.
我向他反抗
I resented him for curbing my appetite.
我讨厌他扼制我的欲望
For a while,I went off on my own.
有一阵子 我离家出走
I wanted to know how it felt to hunt.
我想要知道追寻猎物的感觉
To taste human blood.
想要尝人血的味道
All the men I killed
我杀的所有人
were monsters.
都是恶魔
And so was I.
于是我也成了恶魔
Edward,they were all murderers.
爱德华 他们都是杀人犯
You've probably saved more lives than you've took.
你救的人也许比你杀的人还多
Bella,that's what I've told myself
贝拉 我也是这么告诉自己的
but they were all human beings.
但他们都是活生生的人
I looked into their eyes as they died and saw who I was.
他们临死时 我望着他们的眼睛 看见了我自己
And what I was capable of.
和我的能力
And what I'll be capable of.
我将拥有的能力
Why are you telling me this tonight?
你为什么今晚告诉我这些？
Do you reall think this would change my mind about you?
你真的以为这会改变我对你的看法？
I just wondered if it would change your mind about yourself.
不知道这是否会改变你对自己的看法
And who you'll want see in the mirror a year from now.
你希望一年后在镜中看到怎样的自己
I know I can do this.
我知道我做得到
Let me tell you why,
我来告诉你原因
because you did.
因为你能做到
You should give yourself some credit for that.
这应该有你的功劳
Hopefully a year from now,
希望一年后
I'll look in the mirror and see someone like you.
我在镜子中看到的我就像你一样
Someone capable of courage,sacrifice,and
一个有勇气 愿意牺牲
love.
能够爱的人
- What is that? - Come on! Let's go.
- 什么声音？- 快点 我们走吧
I'm late for my bachelor party.
我该去参加我的告别单身的派对了
Send him out Bella,or we're coming in after him.
放他走吧 贝拉 否则我们就进来拉人了
So this party,will there be strippers?
那么这个派对 会有脱衣舞娘吗？
No,just a couple of mountain lions.
没有 只有一些山狮
Maybe a few bears.
也许有几头熊
Don't worry Bella,we'll get him back in plenty of time.
别担心 贝拉 我们过一阵子会送他回来的
OK go,before they break my house.
快走吧 免得他们把我房子掀了
I'll meet you at the altar.
婚礼上见
I'll be the one in white.
我是穿的白色婚纱的那个
That's very convincing.
真有说服力
What did I say about beauty sleep?
我不是说要睡美容觉的吗？
Sorry. Bad dream.
对不起 做恶梦了
Maybe it's wedding jitters.
可能是婚前紧张症吧
Do you need some help?
需要帮忙吗？
I can do her hair.
我可以帮她弄头发
Really?
真的吗？
Please. I'm not offended by your choice of groom.
拜托 你要跟谁结婚 关我什么事
Just my blatant lack of respect for mortality.
只是觉得我不尊重道德界线
Essentially.
基本上是
Weddings,they bring everyone together!
婚礼 会让大家走到一起的
Hey,Phil,did you find our daughter?
嘿 菲尔 你有看到我们的女儿吗？
Are those graduation caps?
这是毕业帽吗？
Hah! How creative!
哈 好有创意
- Or weird. - Alice? Bella?
- 或者古怪 - 爱丽丝？贝拉？
In here,Mom.
在这儿 妈
Oh my gosh! You're so beautiful!
哦 天啊 你真美
Crap! My mascara.
该死 我的睫毛膏
Thanks!
谢谢
Charlie,get in here!
查理 快过来
You sure? I don't wanna ...
确定吗？我可不想…
I know. I look hot.
我知道 我看上去很精神
We've thought you needed something blue.
我们觉得你需要一件蓝色的东西
And something old.
还要够老
- Besides your mother. - Ah,nice...
- 除你妈妈之外 - 哦 够损…
- It was grandma Swan's. - But we added the sapphires.
- 这是斯旺奶奶的 - 不过我们镶上了蓝宝石
It's beautiful you guys!
真漂亮啊
Wow. Thank you so much.
哇 非常感谢
It's your first family heirloom.
这是你的第一件传家宝
Pass it on to your daughter,and her daughter.
传给你的女儿 还有女儿的女儿
Mom,I love it.
妈妈 我喜欢
No! No smudging my masterpiece!
别 别破坏了我的杰作
She's right.
她说得对
Thank you.
谢谢
It's time for the dress!
该穿婚纱了
- Do you want to see it? - I wanna see!
- 你们想要看看吗？- 我想看
They've got to be related.
他们肯定是一家人
What a gene pool!
多优良的基因库啊
Seriously.
不是盖的
You've got some drool.
你…流口水了
So,do you think Bella will be showing?
你认为贝拉会现身吗？
Jess,she is not pregnant.
杰西 她没怀孕
Okay! Who else gets married at 18?
好吧 还有谁18岁就结婚的？
Ready?
准备好了吗？
Yeah...
是的…
Just don't let me fall,Dad.
别让我摔倒 老爸
Never.
绝对不会
Ladies and gentlemen,we're gathered here on this glorious day
女士们先生们 在这个大喜的日子 我们欢聚一堂
to witness the union of
一同见证爱德华·卡伦
Edward Cullen and Bella Swan.
和贝拉·斯旺这对新人的结合
Please repeat after me.
请跟我说
"I,Edward Cullen."
我 爱德华·卡伦
I,Edward Cullen.
"Take you,Bella Swan."
将与你 贝拉·斯旺
Take you,Bella Swan.
"To have and to hold."
永结同心
To have and to hold.
For better or for worse.
不论好坏
For richer or for poorer.
不论富有或贫苦
In sickness and in health.
不论疾病或健康
To love.
都彼此相爱
To cherish.
并相互珍惜
As long as we both shall live.
直到永远
I do.
我愿意
I love you.
我爱你
I just thought it would be bigger.
我原以为会再大些
Hi guys.
嗨 你们好
We were just saying how pretty everything is. We were all just saying.
我们才在聊这里真漂亮
Thanks so much. You don't think it's too much?
太谢谢了 你们不觉得太铺张了吗？
No! Not at all.
没有 完全没有
Hey man! Nice to see you.
嘿 哥们 很高兴见到你
I'm happy for you.Thank you!
我替你高兴 谢谢
I hope you'll be happy,Bella.
我希望你幸福 贝拉
Thank you,Billy.
谢谢你 比利
Have you heard from him?
你有他的消息吗？
I'm sure Jake wishes you the best.
我肯定杰克会祝福你的
Well,I plan on getting drunk.
我要去喝个痛快了
They're serving some pretty fancy champagne. Sue,can I get you a glass?
他们准备的香槟很不错 苏珊 要我帮你拿一杯吗？
Sparkling is fine with her.
她喝起泡葡萄酒就好
Sounds great.
好极了
Bella!
贝拉
- Congratulations! - Thank you.
- 恭喜 - 谢谢
Eleazar and Carmen,right?
艾丽莎和卡门 对吗？
And these are cousins from Alaska. Tanya and Kate.
这些是来自阿拉斯加的表兄弟 塔尼亚和凯特
We've heard so much about you!
我们听到很多关于你的事了
Welcome to the family.
欢迎加入大家庭
Thank you.
谢谢
Irina.
易瑞娜
Come meet Bella.
来见见贝拉
- I can't do this. - You've promised.
- 我做不到 - 你答应过
They've invited one...
他们邀请了一个…
Irina,he is our friend.
易瑞娜 他是我们的朋友
They killed Laurent.
他们杀了劳伦特
He tried to kill Bella.
他想要杀贝拉
I don't believe that! He wanted to be like us.
我不相信 他想要和我们一样
To live in peace with humans,
与人类和平共处
with me.
跟我相守
I'm sorry.
对不起
Irina!
易瑞娜
Let's not monopolize the bride.
我们不要把持着新娘了
- Congratulations! - Thank you.
- 恭喜 - 谢谢
Sorry.
对不起
What's a wedding without family drama?
没有家族闹剧 哪叫婚礼？
Excuse me. Is this on?
对不起 这开了吗？
Hello!
大家好
I'd like to propose a toast,
我想要举杯敬酒
to my new sister.
敬我的新弟妹
Bella,I hope you've got enough sleep these last 18 years
贝拉 我希望你在过去的18年里睡眠充足
cause you won't be getting anymore for a while.
因为你可能有一阵子没法好好睡了
Bella was just like everybody else
贝拉和大家一样
totally mesmerized by Edward.
完全迷上了爱德华
Or "The Hair" as I called him.
或者说"头发" 这是我给他起的外号
And then suddenly,Edward is all about Bella.
突然之间 爱德华爱上了贝拉
Although she's not captain of the volleyball team.
尽管她不是排球队队长
I'm just kidding.
我只是开开玩笑
Or the president of the Student Council.
也不是学生会主席
Edward will be a good husband.
爱德华会是一个好丈夫
I know this because...
我知道这个是因为…
I'm a cop.
我是警察
I know things.
我什么都知道
Like how to hunt somebody
比如怎么抓捕犯人
till the ends of the earth.
追到天涯海角
Now that you're my sister...
既然你是我的姐姐
You have to get over your aversion to fashion.
你就得克服对时装的反感
And I know how to use a gun.
我知道怎么用枪
Skirts,heels,and handbags.
短裙 高跟鞋和手袋
"Go to sleep,my love.
睡吧 我的宝贝
Go to sleep.
睡吧
When you wake,
当你醒来
you'll see me."
你会看见我
I'd like to thank Renee and Charlie
我想要谢谢蕾妮和查理
for bringing such a wonderful person into the world.
让这么出色的人来到人世间
And into our lives.
带到我们的生命中
We'll cherish and protect her forever.
我们会永远珍惜 保护她
It's an extraordinary thing
非同寻常的是
to meet someone who you can bare your soul to.
能遇见一个你能敞开心扉的人
They'll accept you for what you are.
他们会接受你的一切
I've been waiting what seems like a very long time
我等待了很长的时间
to get beyond what I am.
才能够超越自我
With Bella,
有了贝拉
I feel like I can finally begin.
我才感到人生终于可以开始了
So I'd like to propose a toast to my beautiful bride.
在此向我美丽的新娘敬酒
No measure of time with you will be long enough,
跟你在一起的时光永远嫌不够
but let's start with forever.
但让我们从"永恒"开始
Another of your gifts has just arrived.
你还有一份礼物刚到
What?
什么？
Come on...
跟我来…
What's a wedding present doing in here?
什么婚礼礼物会在这里？
It's a little more private.
这样比较隐密一点
The best man didn't have time to get a tux.
伴郎还没时间准备燕尾服
Jacob!
雅各布
Jacob.
Hey!
嘿
- Hey Bella. - Hey.
- 嘿 贝拉 - 嘿
It was kind of you.
你真是好人
Kind is my middle name.
人好是我的座右铭
I'll see if Rosalie wants to dance.
我看看罗莎莉想不想跳舞
I'm sorry I'm late.
对不起迟到了
It doesn't matter.
没关系
Everything is perfect now.
现在一切都很好
Dance with me?
想要跟我跳支舞吗？
Where have you been?
你去哪里了？
We were gonna put your face on a milk carton.
们都要张贴寻人启事了
Mostly northern Canada.
大多数时间在加拿大北部
I think.
我想是这样
It's weird to be back on two legs again,
能够重新直立行走真是奇怪
with clothes.
还穿着衣服
I fell out of practice with the whole human thing.
我很久没有过人的生活了
Are you okay,
你现在在这里
being here?
还好吧？
Why? Afraid I'll trash your party?
怎么？怕我踢场子啊？
You're not the only one.
又不是只有你一个
You'd think I'd be used to telling you goodbye by now.
你该认为我现在已经习惯和你说再见了
Come on,you're not supposed to be the one crying,Bella.
哭的人不该是你 贝拉
Everyone cries at weddings.
谁在结婚时不掉泪
This is how I'll remember you.
这样我会只记得哭泣的你
Pink cheeks.
粉红的脸蛋
Two left feet.
笨手笨脚
Heart beat.
心跳
So what,soon I'm gonna be dead to you?
所以很快地你就不再当我是活人？
No.
没有
I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm trying to appreciate your last night as human.
我只是很珍惜你身为人类的最后一晚
It's not my last night.
这不是我的最后一夜
What? I thought you...
什么？我以为你
I didn't really wanna spend my honeymoon writhing in pain.
我不想我的蜜月在痛苦中渡过
What's the point?
什么意思？
It's not like you're gonna have a real honeymoon with him.
反正跟他一起又不会有个真正的蜜月之旅
It will be as real as any other.
会和任何其它蜜月一样真实
That's a sick joke.
这是什么玩笑话
You're joking?
你在开玩笑吧？
What? While you're still human?
什么？在你还是人类之身时蜜月？
You can't be serious Bella. Tell me you're not that stupid?
你不是认真的 贝拉 告诉我你没那么傻？
I mean it's really none of your business.
真的不关你的事
- No,you can't do this. - Jake...
- 不 你不能这么做 - 杰克…
- Listen to me,Bella. - Let me go!
- 听我说 贝拉 - 放开我
Jacob,calm down.
雅克布 冷静一点
Are you out of your mind? Huh? You'll kill her!
你疯了吗？你会杀了她
Jake,walk away.
杰克 走开
Enough,Jacob!
够了 雅各布
Stay out of this,Sam.
你别管 山姆
You're not gonna start something that we'll have to finish.
别闯祸了让我们帮你擦屁股
- She'll die! - She's not our concern anymore.
- 她会死的 - 这不关我们的事了
Let's go,Seth!
走吧 赛斯
- I'm really stupid. - No,it's alright.
- 我真傻 - 不 没关系
They probably miss us. Let's go back.
他们可能惦记我们了 我们回去吧
He won't tell you where he's taking you?
他不肯告诉你他要带你去哪里？
No,it's surprise.
是啊 他想给我惊喜
Well,wear a hat and use sunscreen.
好 戴上帽子 涂涂防晒霜
- Take care. - I will.
- 小心点 - 我会的
OK.
好的
I love you,Bella.
我爱你 贝拉
I love you!
我也爱你
So much.
非常爱
Thank you.
谢谢
Everything is packed and ready to go.
东西都打包好了 随时可以出发
Cool.
太棒了
- I'll go see him. - Yeah.
- 我去看他 - 好的
Dad...
老爸…
Well...
好吧
It's gonna be strange,
可能会比较奇怪
You're not living under my roof.
你不住在我这里了
Yeah...
是的
It will be strange for me,too.
我也会觉得奇怪
You know it'll always be your home,right?
你知道这里永远是你的家 对吗？
I love you,Dad.
我爱你 爸爸
Forever.
永远
I love you too,Bella.
我也爱你 贝拉
I always have and always will.
一直爱 永远爱
Alright...
好吧
Go on. Don't want to miss your plane.
走吧 别赶不上飞机
Wherever it's going.
不管是去哪里
OK...
好的
Goodbye.
再见
Ready?
准备好了？
Yeah,I'm ready.
好了
Pare o carro.
[葡萄牙语] 请靠边停车
So we're not staying in Rio?
我们不住在里约热内卢？
No,just passing through.
不 只是路过
Are we close?
快到了吗？
That's Isle Esme.
那是埃斯梅岛
It was a gift from Carlisle.
这是卡莱尔的礼物
Is this totally necessary?
真的有必要吗？
I'm nothing if not traditional.
如果不传统就不是我了
Want to take a look around?
要四处转转吗？
Are you tired?
你累吗？
Want a swim?
想游泳吗？
Yeah,sounds nice.
听上去不错
I need a few minutes as a human.
身为人类 我需要几分钟准备一下
Don't delay,Mrs. Cullen.
别拖太久 卡伦太太
OK.
好的
OK...
Alice!
爱丽丝
Don't be a coward.
别做胆小鬼
You're so beautiful!
你真漂亮
I promise that we'd try,
我答应我们可以试试
but if this doesn't work...
但是如果不成功
I trust you.
我信任你
It's OK.
没事的
Bella,you're hurt
贝拉 你受伤了
What?
什么？
No,Bella. Look.
不 贝拉 看
I can't tell you how sorry I am.
我真的非常抱歉
I'm not.
我没有
Really,I'm not. I'm fine...
真的 我没有 我很好
Don't say you're fine.
别说你很好
Just don't.
不要
No,you don't!
Don't ruin this.
别扫兴
I've already ruined it.
我已经扫兴了
Why can't see you how perfectly happy I am?
你难道看不出我有多快乐吗？
Or was,five seconds ago.
或者说 五秒钟之前是这样
Now I'm sorta pissed off actually.
现在我真的有点生气了
Well,you should be angry with me.
你应该对我生气
We knew this was going to be tricky,right?
我们知道这很蹊跷
I think we did amazing.
我认为我们做的很棒
It was amazing for me.
对我来说很棒
That's what you're worried about?
这就是你所担心的？
That I didn't enjoy myself?
怕我不开心？
I know it's not the same for you but
我知道对你来说不同 但
for a human...
对人来说
I can't imagine it gets better.
我想不出还有什么比这更好了
Last night was the best night of my existence.
昨晚是我有生以来最美好的夜晚
It was the best.
是最美好的
You're not gonna touch me again,are you?
你不会再碰我 是吗？
You know that's not what I meant.
你知道我不是这个意思
Let me make you breakfast.
我来为你做早餐吧
I win.
我赢了
Bella.
贝拉
You having a nightmare?
你做恶梦了？
No.
没
It was just a dream.
只是一个梦
It was a really good dream.
一个很美的梦
Then why are you crying?
那你为什么哭呢？
I wanted it to be real.
我希望它是真实的
Tell me.
告诉我
Bella,I can't.
贝拉 我不能
Please...
求你了
Maybe they'll say she was in a car crash.
也许他们会说她遇上车祸了
Or tripped and fell off a cliff.
或者失足从悬崖摔落
At least,I'll get one thing out of it.
至少我能想明白一点
No you won't.
你不能
The Cullens are not a danger to the town or tribe.
卡伦一家对小镇或部落没有危险
He will kill her or change her.
他会杀了她或把她变成吸血鬼
- And the treaty says... - I say,Jacob.
- 约定里说 - 是我说的 雅各布
I say.
我说的
You know if you wanted things different,you should've become Alpha.
你要想事态有所改变 你就该采取行动
Turning it down seemed like a good idea at the time.
现在看来拒绝是个好办法
Jake,you really think you could kill Bella if she comes back as a vampire?
杰克 你真的觉得如果贝拉回来变成吸血鬼 你会杀她吗？
No. He would make one of us do it,then hold a grudge against...
不会 他会让我们其中一个动手 然后怨恨…
Shut up,Leah.
住嘴 莉娅
Would you just get over it?
你就不能忘了她吗？
It's not like you imprinted on her.
你和她又不是命中注定
At least they seem happy.
至少他们看上去很幸福
Yeah. Some people are just lucky,I guess
是的 有些人就是幸运
Lucky?
幸运？
None of them belong to themselves anymore.
他们都不再属于自己了
And the sickest part is?
最恶心的部分是
Their genes tell them they're happy.
他们的基因告诉他们自己很幸福
At least if you imprinted on someone,you'll finally forget Bella.
至少当你爱上其他人 你就会把贝拉忘记的
I mean,being any kind of happy is better
我是说 只要快乐 总好过
than being miserable about someone you can't have.
为一个得不到的人而伤心
Bella,these are our housekeepers,Gustavo and Kaure.
贝拉 这两位是我们的管家 古斯塔沃和卡拉
This is my wife,Bella.
这是我妻子贝拉
Nice to meet you.
很高兴认识您
Guess,we should just leave them to it.
也许我们该随他们去
What was that about?
这是为什么？
She's afraid of you.
她怕你
Why?
为什么？
Because I have you here all alone.
因为我和你一个人在这里
Wait,she knows about you?
等等 她知道你的事？
She suspects.
她怀疑
She's native Ticuna.
她是提卡纳土著
They have legends of blood drinking demons
他们的传说有讲到吸血恶魔
who prey on beautiful women.
专门诱骗漂亮女人
Monster.
恶魔
I've gone to the mainland to hunt,be back befor you wake
我去内陆狩猎了 会在你醒来之前回来
You are late.
你动作太慢了
Bella.
贝拉
Don't come in here.
别进来
You don't need to see this.
你不该看到这个
In sickness and in health,remember?
无论疾病或健康 还记得吗？
It must have been the chicken.
一定是因为鸡肉
Will you grab my bag?
你能把我的包拿过来吗？
What is it?
什么？
How many days it has been since the wedding?
婚礼过去几天了？
14,why?
14天 怎么了？
Will you tell me what's going on?
你能告诉我怎么了吗？
I'm late.
我来晚了
My period is late.
我的大姨妈来晚了
That's impossible.
这不可能
Can this happen?
这种事会发生吗？
- Alice. - Bella,are you alright?
- 爱丽丝 - 贝拉 你还好吗？
- I'm not one hundred percent sure. - Why? What's wrong?
- 我不确定 - 为什么？出什么问题了？
- I just... - You just what?
- 我刚… - 你刚什么？
- Alice,what did you see? - Here's Carlisle.
- 爱丽丝 你看到什么？- 我是卡莱尔
Bella,what's going on?
贝拉 发生什么事？
I'm a little worried. Can vampires go into shock?
我有点担心 吸血鬼也会震惊吗？
- Has anyone being harmed? - No.
- 有人受伤了？- 没有
I know it's impossible,but I think I'm pregnant.
我知道不可能 但我觉得我怀孕了
Carlisle,I swear something just moved inside me.
卡莱尔 我发誓我身体内刚才有东西在动
- Is this even possible? - I don't know.
- 这有可能吗？- 我不知道
What is he saying?
他说什么？
The sooner she is here,the sooner we can find out what it is.
她越快回来 我们就能越快找到原因
- I need you to get to the mainland at once. - Yeah,I will.
- 我要你马上回到内陆 - 我会的
Well?
怎么样？
Damn it...
该死
Kaure is making sure that you're still alive.
卡拉想确保你是不是还活着
What did you do with her?
你对她做了什么？
What do you know about this?
你知道些什么？
I know that you're a demon!
我知道你是个魔鬼
You've killed this little girl!
你杀了这个小姑娘
What?
说什么？
People have legends. You've seen this before.
人们由他们自己的传说 你已经看到了
Please. Tell me how to help her.
求你了 告诉我该如何救她
You only do bad.
你只会做坏事
I'm begging you.
我在求你
I'll do anything.
我什么都愿意
I love her.
我爱她
Please.
求你了
Tell me how she can survive this.
告诉我她怎样才能活下去
Death.
死亡
I will not let it hurt you.
我不会让它伤害你的
Carlisle will get that thing out.
卡莱尔会把那个东西弄出来
"Thing"?
"东西"？
Wait here while we load.
我们装东西的时候你等在这儿
- Hello. - Rosalie.
- 喂 - 罗莎莉
Bella?
贝拉
- What's going on? - I need your help.
- 怎么啦？- 我需要你的帮助
Hey,son.
嘿 孩子
What's going on?
怎么啦？
Bella called him.
贝拉给他打电话了
Hey,I haven't seen you in a while.
嘿 我有一阵子没见你了
- Are you OK? - So you finally heard from Bella?
- 你还好吗？- 你终于有贝拉的消息了？
They've extended their trip.
他们延长了行程
It seems she caught a bug.
她好像感染了病毒
They wanna wait until she feels better before they travel.
他们想等她感觉好些再出发
She's sick...
她病了
Yeah,she told me not to worry,but she sounded...
是的 她叫我不要担心 但她听上去
I don't know,off.
我不知道 她有点心不在焉
She'll be fine,Charlie.
她会没事的 查理
Come on. Let's eat.
来吧 吃饭
Jacob.
雅各布
Let it go...
别管了
- Is it true? - Hello,Jacob. How are you?
- 真的吗？- 嘿 雅各布 你好吗？
Listen,just give it to me straight.
听着 跟我说实话
Jake,is that you?
杰克 是你吗？
- She's here? - They came home 2 weeks ago.
- 她在这里？- 他们两周前回来的
Jake...
杰克
I'm glad you came.
我很高兴你能来
- Close enough. - What's your problem?
- 够近了 - 关你什么事？
Rose,it's okay.
露丝 没关系
You look terrible.
你看上去真糟糕
Yeah,it's nice to see you,too.
是的 我也很高兴见到你
So are you going to tell me what's wrong with you?
你能告诉我你怎么了吗？
Rose,do you wanna help me up?
露丝 你能扶我起来吗？
You did this!
你干的好事
I didn't know it was even possible.
我根本不知道会有可能
- What is it? - I'm not sure.
- 是什么？- 我不确定
Ultrasound and needles won't penetrate the embryo sack.
超声波和针都无法穿透胚胎
I can't see it either,
我也看不到
and I can't see Bella's future anymore,
我也无法再看到贝拉的未来
We've been researching legends,but there isn't much to go on.
我们研究了传说 但是没有太多线索
What we do know is that it's strong and fast growing.
我们所知道的是它很结实 长得很快
Why haven't you done anything?!
你们为什么不能做点什么？
Take it out of her!
把它从她身体内取出来
This is none of your business,dog!
这不关你的事 狗
Rose!
露丝
- All this fighting isn't good for Bella. - The fetus isn't good for Bella.
- 吵架对贝拉没有好处 - 这个胎儿对贝拉没有好处
Say the word,Alice. "Baby." It's just a little baby.
爱丽丝 叫它"宝宝" 它只是个小宝宝
Possibly.
有可能
Carlisle,you've got to do something.
卡莱尔 你需要做点什么
No.
不
It's not his decision,it's not any of yours.
这不是他的决定 也不是你们任何人的
Jacob,I need to talk to you.
雅各布 我需要和你谈谈
I always knew you would destroy her.
我就知道你会毁了她
She thinks Carlisle can turn her at the last minute.
她认为卡莱尔能够在最后一刻改变她
As he did with me and Esme.
就像他对我和Esme所做的一样
- Can he? - The probability is slight.
- 他可以吗？- 可能性很小
If her heart fails...
如果她心力衰竭
Look,Jacob,I need you to do something for me.
听着 雅各布 我需要你帮我做件事
For her?
为她呢？
You have a connection with her that I'll never understand.
你和她的关系是我永远无法理解的
Maybe you could talk to her,
也许你可以和她谈
change her mind.
让她回心转意
You could keep her alive.
你能让她活下来
And if I can't?
如果我做不到呢？
If she dies,
如果她死了
you'll get what you've always wanted...
你可以如愿以偿
To kill me.
杀了我
Rose,I'm fine. Really.
露丝 我很好 真的
So Edward sent you to come talk to me?
爱德华派你来和我谈的？
Sort of...
算是吧
Though I can't figure out why he thinks you'd listen to me,
不过我不知道他为什么以为你会听我的
I mean you never have before.
你以前从来没听过
Since when are you and Blondie BFF's?
你什么时候开始和那个金发女人成了好朋友啦？
Rose understands what I want.
露丝明白我想要什么
What are you thinking,Bella?
你在想什么 贝拉？
Seriously.
说实话
I know this seems a scary thing,but
我知道这件事看起来挺可怕 但是…
it's not.
但并非如此
It's like this miracle or something.
这就像个奇迹
I can feel him.
我能感觉到他
So it's a bouncing baby boy.
那么说是个活蹦乱跳的小男孩了
I'm sorry,I don't know. I should've brought blue balloons.
对不起 我不知道 我本该带些蓝气球来
It's just a guess.
只是猜测
When I picture him I see a boy.
我在脑子里想的时候 看到的是一个男孩
We'll see!
到时看吧
- You won't. - Jake,I can do this.
- 不要 - 杰克 我可以做得到
- I'm strong enough. - Come on!
- 我够坚强 - 拜托
You can spout that crap to your bloodsucker,but you don't fool me.
你可以和你那吸血鬼去编这瞎话 但你骗不了我
I can see what that thing is doing to you.
我知道那东西会对你做什么
- It's a killer,Bella! - You're wrong.
- 它会杀了你 贝拉 - 你错了
When you die,what was the point?
当你死的时候 还有什么意义？
Of me loving you,you loving him.
我爱你 你爱他
How's that right for anyone?
这对大家有什么好？
Because I sure don't see it.
因为我显然看不懂
Listen to me,Bella...
听我说 贝拉
Please.
求你了
Just don't do this...
不要这么做
Live,okay?
活下来 好吗？
Please.
求你了
Jake,everything will be okay.
杰克 不会有事的
Jake,don't go.
杰克 别走
I know how this ends.
我知道结局会是怎样
And I'm not sticking around to watch.
我不想眼睁睁看着
Jake,I can do this...
杰克 我能做得到
This is none of your business,dog!
这不关你的事 狗
Jake,don't go...
杰克 别走
You did this...
是你干的
Everything is going to be okay...
一切都会好的
The fetus isn't good for Bella.
胎儿对贝拉没有好处
I know how this ends.
我知道结局会是怎样
...It's killing you.
它会杀了你
Jake!!
杰克
Is it true,Jacob?
是真的吗 雅各布？
It's growing fast.
它长得很快
It's unnatural!
这不正常
Dangerous!
危险
Monstrosity! Abombination!
怪物 孽障
On our land.
在我们的领地上
We can't allow it!!
我们决不容忍
We have to protect the tribe!
我们必须保护部落
What they've bred won't be able to control its thirst.
他们产下的东西将无法抵御饥渴
Every human will be in danger.
所有的人类都将处于危险之中
- We're ready. - We're underway!
- 我们准备好了 - 我们马上出发
Now
现在
We must destroy it before it's born.
我们必须在它出生前消灭它
You mean,kill Bella?
你的意思是杀死贝拉？
Her choice affects us all.
她的选择影响了我们所有人
Bella's human. Our protection applies to her.
贝拉是人类 我们也要保护她
She's dying anyway!
她反正都要死
We have real enemies to fight tonight.
今晚我们要和真正的敌人战斗
Tonight?
今晚？
And you will fight with us,Jake.
你要和我们并肩作战 杰克
I will not!
我不
I am the grandson of Ephraim Black!
我是伊弗雷姆 布莱克的孙子
I'm the grandson of a chief!
我是酋长的孙子
I wasn't born to follow you or anyone else.
我生来就不为追随你或任何其他人的
Don't worry. They're not following us.
别担心 没人跟着我们
What do you think you're doing here?
你在这里干什么？
- I left Sam's pack. - Go home,Seth.
- 我离开山姆的队伍了 - 回家吧 塞斯
- I won't stand behind him. - Oh,yes,you will!
- 我不要跟在他后面 - 不 你要跟
I'm not kidding. Get out of here.
我不是开玩笑 快离开这里
Is that an order?
这是命令吗？
You gonna make me bow down,too?
想要我也俯首帖耳？
I'm not ordering anyone.
我不对任何人下命令
I'm just going off on my own here,okay?
我要一个人去 行吗？
Great!
很好
- And I've got your back. - No,you don't!
- 我给你掩护 - 不可以
If Sam comes after Bella,
如果山姆要抓贝拉
are you really ready to fight your own brother?
你真的已经准备好迎战你的兄弟？
Your sister?
还有姐妹？
If it's the right thing to do.
如果这样做是对的话
Whatever.
随你便
I'm gonna go give the Cullen's the heads up.
我要去提醒卡伦一家
Do what you want.
你自便吧
How cool is this?!
这该多棒啊？
A two man pack!
两个人
- Two against the world. - You're getting on my nerves,Seth.
- 与全世界为敌 - 别把我惹毛了 塞斯
I'll shut up.
我住嘴
Can do.
我做得到
Get ready.
准备好
They're coming for Bella.
他们来找贝拉了
They're not going to touch her.
他们别想碰她一根毫毛
Agreed.
同意
Man,I can smell them all the way out here.
天哪 我大老远就能闻到他们的味道了
What the hell are you doing here?
你们在这里干什么？
I'm not going to let my little brother get himself killed.
我可不想让我弟弟自寻死路
Go away,Leah! I'll take care of myself.
走开 莉娅 我能照顾好自己
That you think so proves that you need a babysitter.
你真想证明给你姐看
Will both of you shut up?
你们两个都住嘴行吗？
- Sam send you? - Sam doesn't even know I left.
- 山姆派你来的？- 山姆根本不知道我走了
I think he's just figured it out.
我猜他刚刚发觉了
Jake...
杰克
I know what his plan is.
我知道他的计划
Sam's lost the element of surprise
山姆没法出其不意了
and he doesn't wanna take you on outnumbered.
他不想在数量上压倒你们
So he's not gonna come at you head on.
所以他不会与你们正面交战
He's got the place surrounded and he'll wait for an opportunity.
他包围了这个地方 准备伺机出击
He won't get through without a fight.
他不打硬仗是进不来的
No fights.
不要硬仗
- We won't be the ones to break the treaty. - The treaty is void.
- 我们不想破坏约定 - 约定无效
- At least in Sam's mind. - Not in ours.
- 至少山姆是这么认为的 - 我们不这么认为
Carlisle,no one's hunted for weeks.
卡莱尔 没有人可以被追猎数周
We'll make do.
我们可以应付
You've done us a great service,Jacob.
你已经帮了我们大忙了 雅各布
Thank you.
谢谢
I know they're out there somewhere,
我知道他们就在附近
but I can't hear them anymore.
但我已经没听到他们的声音了
It's so quiet.
好安静
I've stopped hearing them,too.
就在我决定离开的时候
The second I decided to leave.
我也没听到他们的声音了
It's nice.
很好
- You know you can't stay here. - But I don't have any place...
- 你知道你不能留在这里 - 可我没有地方
I can't trust you with the Cullen's.
我不能相信你对卡伦一家的态度
You hate them too much.
你太恨他们了
- You don't even like me. - I don't have to.
- 你甚至不喜欢我 - 我没这必要
I just have to follow you.
我只要跟着你们
Look,Seth doesn't want you here.
塞斯不要你在这里
Neither do I.
我也不想
Being unwanted isn't exactly a new thing to me.
没人要对我来说不是什么稀奇事
Look,I'll stay out of your way.
我不会碍你们的事
I'll do whatever you want,except go back to Sam's pack
我会照你说的去做 只要不让我回到山姆的队伍
and be the pathetic ex- girlfriend he can't get away from.
做他无法摆脱的可怜的前女友
You don't know how many times I wished I could imprint on someone.
你不知道我有多少次希望我能将某个人铭刻在心
Anyone...
任何人
Just to break the connection.
只是不要跟太紧
Alright...
好吧
I'm gonna do a perimeter around.
我要四处巡视一下
Got my flank?
一起去吗？
(不死身孩子)
(吸血鬼孩子)
Her rib is cracked,
她的肋骨裂开了
but they're no splinters.
但没有裂成碎片
It hasn't punctured anything.
它没有刺穿任何东西
- Yet... - Edward.
- 目前还没有 - 爱德华
It's breaking her bones now.
它现在正在破坏她的骨头
It's crushing you from the inside out.
它从里面向外挤压着你
Carlisle,tell her what you told me.
卡莱尔 把你和我说的也告诉她吧
Tell her.
告诉她
Carlisle,tell me.
卡莱尔 告诉我
It's alright.
没事的
The fetus isn't compatible with your body.
你的身体容不下这个胎儿
It's too strong.
它太强壮了
It won't allow you to get the nutrition you need.
它让你无法获得你所需的营养
It's starving you by the hour,I can't stop it and I can't slow it down.
它会让你慢慢饿死 我无法阻止 也无法让它放慢速度
At this rate,your heart will give out before you can deliver.
按照这个速度 你的心脏在你临产前就会停止跳动
- Then I'll hold on as long as I can and ... - Bella...
- 那我就尽力坚持 - 贝拉
There are some conditions even venom can't overcome.
有些情况是连吸血鬼的毒液也无法克服的
Do you understand?
你明白吗？
I'm sorry.
对不起
Edward,I'm sorry.
对不起 爱德华
I can't live without you.
我不能没有你
You won't. You'll have a part of me.
不会的 我会留下我的骨肉
He'll need you.
他需要你
Do you honestly think I could love
你真的认为我能够爱它
or even tolerate it,if it killed you?
或容忍它 如果它害死你的话？
It's not his fault.
这不是他的错
- You have to accept what it is. - Because you've given me no choice!
- 你必须接受它 - 因为你没有给我选择
Bella,we're supposed to be partners,remember?
贝拉 我们应该相依为命的 还记得吗？
But you've decided this on your own.
但这一次你却自作主张
You've decided to leave me.
你选择了离开我
- Don't see it that way. - Well I have no other way to see it.
- 别这么想 - 我只能这么想
Cause it's me who'll lose you.
因为失去你的人是我
And I don't choose that.
而这不是我的选择
I don't choose that.
不是我的选择
Are you cold?
你冷吗？
I got it.
我来吧
Don't do that.
不要这样
What?
为什么？
Smile like I'm your favorite person in the world.
不要那样微笑 仿佛我是你在这世界上最喜欢的人
You're one of them.
你是其中的一个
It feels complete when you're here,Jake.
有你在感觉很充实 杰克
We need to find a way to get some food into her system.
我们要想办法让她的胃吸收些东西
- If only I could see the fetus, - Baby.
- 只要我能看到胎儿的话 - 宝宝
Maybe I could figure out what it wants.
也许我就能知道它想要什么
I think you might be right.
我认为你可能说得对
Jacob just had an idea.
雅各布倒是有个主意
It wasn't an idea,it was a snide comment.
不是什么主意 只是个恶毒的意见
What were you thinking?
你在想什么？
That it's probably just looking for someone to sink its teeth into.
也许它只是想要用牙齿咬着什么人
He's thirsty?
他渴了？
I know the feeling.
我知道那种感觉
If it's craving,it's not gonna want animal blood.
如果它渴了的话 它不会想要动物的血
I have some Type O negative laid aside for Bella.
我给贝拉留了一些O型阴性血
Walk with me?
和我去走走吗？
Wait! Wait! Wait! You're going to make her drink that?
等等 你要让她喝那个？
It's the fastest way to test the theory.
这是最快的测试方法
Only if you're comfortable with it.
只要你不介意的话
I'll try anything.
我什么都愿意试
Just hold on...
等等
I think I'm going to be sick.
我想我可能要吐了
It'll make it a little easier to take.
这样喝起来会方便些
It tastes...
这味道
Good.
很好
Your pulse is already getting stronger.
你的脉搏已经变强了
It's working.
有效果了
- You sound better. - I am.
- 你听起来好些了 - 是的
I feel much better.
我感觉好多了
This whole thing must have put a kink in the honeymoon,huh?
这一切一定搅乱了你们的蜜月 对吗？
You could say that...
可以这么说
Otherwise married life treating you OK?
其它方面的婚后生活你感觉还好吗？
Edward still walks on water and all that?
爱德华还是水上飘吗？
Yeah,I mean it is different now.
是的 我是说现在的情况不同了
The important thing is that you're better and that you're coming home soon. Right?
重要的是你好多了 马上就要回家了 对吗？
Okay,Dad,I don't want you to freak out
好吧 爸爸 我不想吓到你
but...
不过
I'm going to a medical center in Switzerland.
我要去瑞士的一个医疗中心
What?! You're not going to Switzerland!
什么？你要去瑞士
- You said you were better! - I am.
- 你不是说你好些了吗 - 是的
No Bella,I'm getting on a plane.
不 贝拉 我坐飞机来
No!It's really more of a ...a spa.
别这样 真的就只是像做一次…水疗
And I'm sure I'll be better before you got there.
我肯定你来之前我就会好多了
I...uh...I don't know
我…我不知道
Dad,don't come.
爸爸 不要来
Picture me healthy.
就当我很健康
Like I'm sitting on the couch with you,eating pizza or something.
仿佛我和你一起坐在沙发上 吃着比萨什么的
You want me to visualize?
你要我想象？
They say it helps.
他们说这管用
Just picture me like that.
就这么想象着我
Like I was.
仿佛我就在那里
It'll make me feel better.
这样能让我感觉舒服些
Dad,I gotta go. OK?
爸 我先挂了 好吗？
Bella...
贝拉
- I love you. - Bella...
- 我爱你 - 贝拉
Sorry I've been so angry.
对不起我发这么大的火
I would be too.
换了我也会
I've left you alone in this.
我让你一个人来承受这一切
Marriage.
婚姻
They say the first year is the hardest.
他们说第一年是最难的
- What was that? - What?
- 什么声音？- 什么？
I thought I've just heard.
我好像刚刚听到
Just say something else...
再说点别的什么
Like what?
比如什么？
Edward,what's going on?
爱德华 怎么了？
He likes the sound of your voice.
他喜欢你的声音
You can hear him?
你能听到他？
Mind.
想法
He likes my voice as well.
他也喜欢我的声音
What?
什么？
What do you hear?
你听到什么？
So strange...
好奇怪
I thought he was like me,but he's not,he's like you.
我以为他像我 其实他像你
Good and pure.
善良 纯洁
He's happy.
他很高兴
Of course you are.
你当然高兴
Of course you're happy. How can you not be?
你当然高兴 你怎么会不高兴呢？
I love you so much!
我好爱你
What do you hear now?
现在你听到什么？
He loves you,Bella.
他爱你 贝拉
Oh my gosh!
哦 天哪
Jacob.
雅各布
So that's the last of it?
这是最后一包了吗？
Bella can deliver as early as tomorrow
贝拉可能明天就会生产
If she's going to have any chance at all she'll need more blood.
如果她想要任何成功的机会的话 她需要更多的血
You need to feed.
你需要进食
You have to be at your strongest for her. We need to go tonight.
为了她 你必须保持最佳状态 我们今晚需要走
Carlisle,you're the enemy now.
卡莱尔 你现在成了他们的敌人了
Sam won't hesitate. You will be slaughtered.
山姆不会手软 你会被宰杀
Emmett will come with us.
埃米特会和我们一起去
- That won't be enough. - We have no choice,Jacob.
- 那不够 - 我们没有选择 雅各布
If there's anything we can do to save her,we have to try.
只要有办法能救她 我们都要尝试
You would risk your lives for her?
你们会为她冒生命危险吗？
Of course we would.
我们当然会
Bella's part of our family now.
贝拉现在已经是我们家庭的成员了
Yeah.
是的
I can see that.
我看得出来
This really is a family.
你们确实是一家人
As strong as the one I was born into.
就像我所出生的家庭一样强大
I know what I have to do.
我知道我该做什么
Jake,they're coming!
杰克 他们来了
- I know. - We should phase,Jacob.
- 我知道 - 我们应该变身 雅各布
We can't protect ourselves like this.
我们这样没法保护自己
They'll see us as a threat.
他们会把我们看作威胁
I wanna talk!
我要和他们谈谈
Be easier if I could hear you,too.
如果你们现身的话会更方便些
This isn't your territory anymore.
这里不再是你的领地了
How's your new family working out?
你的新家怎么样了？
You done?
你说完了没有？
You coming home,Jake?
你要回家吗 杰克？
Not until I finish this.
等我了结这个
What do you mean?
你什么意思
I want Sam to take back Leah and Seth.
我要山姆把莉娅和塞斯带回去
- What? - No way!
- 什么？- 没门
Be quiet.
安静点
I want them safe and I want this over.
我要他们安全 我也要此事结束
I need Sam to wait until Bella's been separated from the problem.
我要山姆等到贝拉摆脱这个孽障时
- You mean until she's dead? - Ease up,Paul.
- 你是说等她死后？- 放轻松 保罗
Then what?
然后怎样？
Tell Sam that when the moment comes,
告诉山姆到那时候
I'll be the one to destroy it.
我会亲手消灭那东西
Jake!
杰克
I'm the only one who can.
只有我能做到
They trust me.
他们信任我
You've played us!
你耍了我们
Thank you.
谢谢你
- They make it out alright? - Yeah.
- 他们都好吧？- 是的
Good.
很好
Hey...
嘿
Are you OK?
你还好吧？
Yeah,it's not like I'm not one carrying a demon.
好啊 又不是我怀着一个恶魔
This is pretty important,Bella.
这很重要 贝拉
Why don't you tell Jacob what you've decided to?
为什么不告诉雅各布你的决定呢？
What now?
现在又怎么了？
Rose is trying to talk Bella out of her baby names.
露丝想要说服贝拉放弃她给孩子取的名字
She hates them.
她不喜欢
Well then I'm on your side no matter what you pick.
不管你选什么我都支持你
They are not that bad.
我取的名字没那么糟糕
If it's a boy,E.J.
如果是男孩 就叫E.J.
Edward Jacob.
爱德华 雅各布
Fine,that one isn't awful.
行 这名字还不赖
Why don't you tell him the girl's name?
你干嘛不告诉他女孩的名字？
I was playing around with our mom's names.
我想结合我们妈妈的名字
Renee and Esme.
蕾妮和埃斯米
I was thinking Renesmee.
我想给她取名 莱妮斯米
R- Renesmee?
叫莱妮斯米？
Too weird?
太怪了？
It's not too weird.
不是很怪
It's beautiful!
很美
And it's unique.
也很特别
It certainly fits the situation.
也很符合情况
I like Renesmee.
我喜欢莱妮斯米
He likes it.
他喜欢
Rosalie,pass the morphine.
罗莎莉 把吗啡递过来
Carlisle said that the placenta must have detached.
卡莱尔说胎盘一定已经脱落
- He's coming as fast as he can. - We'll have to do it.
- 他会尽快赶过来 - 我们必须动手了
Rose,let the morphine spread.
露丝 让吗啡先扩散
There's no time. He's dying.
没时间了 孩子会死的
Get him out now!
快把他取出来
Look at me,Bella.
看着我 贝拉
Rosalie,don't!
罗莎莉 不要
Alice,get her out of here!
爱丽丝 带她出去
Rosalie!
罗莎莉
- Save her! You gotta change her! - I can't! Not whilst he's still in there.
- 救救她 你得转化她的 - 不行 孩子还在里面
I gotta get him out first.
我要先把孩子弄出来
Stay focused. Keep your heart beating.
集中精神 保持心跳
He's suffocating!
他窒息了
It's Renesmee!
是莱妮斯米
You're beautiful!
你真美
Bella?
贝拉
Bella?!
Jacob,take the baby.
雅各布 抱着孩子
Keep that away from me.
别让它靠近我
Edward.
爱德华
I'll take care of her.
我来照顾她
I promise I'm okay,let me.
我发誓我没问题 让我来吧
What's that?
那是什么？
My venom.
我的毒液
It supposed to be working.
应该有用的
I won't kill you...
我不会杀你
That would be too easy.
那样就便宜了你
You deserve to live with this.
你该活着承受这一切
She didn't make it...
她没挺过来
I'm not dead. You're not dead...
我没死 你也没有死
Come on!
快呀
No. It will work.
不 会有用的
Please,please...
求你了
Come back to me please...
快醒过来
Bella,please.
贝拉 求你了
I don't care what he's done.
我不管他做了什么
He's still my son.
他始终是我儿子
I'm sorry,Billy.
对不起 比利
I just thought you should know.
我只是觉得你该知道
Bella is dead.
贝拉死了
It killed her.
那东西害死了她
Let's go!
我们走
It's like gravity.
像是不可抗拒的力量
Your whole center shifts.
是你的世界为之改变
Suddenly,it's not the earth holding you here.
突然之间 支撑你的不再是这个世界
You would do anything,
你愿意做任何事情
be anything she needs.
只要她需要
A Friend.
朋友
A Brother.
兄弟
A Protector.
保护者
Alice! Jasper!
爱丽丝
You'll be fine.
你会没事的
- We're outnumbered. - By a lot.
- 他们人多 - 差距悬殊
I won't let them hurt my family.
我不会让他们伤害我的家人
Stop! It's over.
住手 结束了
If you kill her,you kill me.
如果你要杀她 就先杀我
Jacob imprinted.
雅各布将她铭记了
They can't hurt her.
他们不会伤害她的
Whomever a wolf imprints on can't be harmed.
只要被狼人铭记着 就不会受到伤害
It's their most absolute law.
这是他们的不可抗拒的规矩
She shouldn't be so still.
她不应该毫无反应
It's the morphine.
是吗啡的原因
- Maybe it was too late. - No,Edward.
- 也许是太晚了 - 不 爱德华
Listen to her heart.
听她的心跳
It's from Carlisle.
是卡莱尔寄来的
Which is spelled with an "S" sweet Bianca.
拼写里应该带有一个S 亲爱的比安卡
He's added a new member to his coven.
他家又添丁了
Increasing his power.
他的势力提升了
First it's the spelling and the grammar.
首先是拼写和语法的问题
At least our dispute with the Cullens is over.
至少我们与卡伦一家的争端已经结束
Over?
结束？
Goodness no...
天哪 不…
Our dispute goes far beyond the fate of a mere human.
我们的争议远非一个凡人的命运
And what might it be?
会是什么？
I thought you understood
我还以为你明白
They have something I want.
他们有我想要的东西